我叫麦克斯 是你们的服务员
I'm Max. I'll be your waitress,
因为我不做顾客背景调查 谁都收
'cause I don't do background checks here.
你是我们的服务员吗 从你的制服
Oh, you'll be our waitress. I never guessed that
以及写着麦克斯的名牌上看 完全猜不出呢
based on the uniform and name tag that says "Max."
你知道我一小时挣3块钱吧
You know I make, like, $3, right?
我知道这对从1920年来的你们来说
I realize that's a lot of money in the 1920s
可是一笔巨款呢
where you two are from.
请帮我们把酒打开 并拿两个干净酒杯来
Here, open this and bring us two clean glasses.
好的 不太了不起的盖茨比
Sure, not-so-great Gatsby.
OJ与妮可
Hey, OJ and Nicole.
第十桌有两个装逼的人 懂啥意思吧
Rude snobs at table ten. You know what that means.
换酒大作战吗
Wine swap?
走起
Let's roll.
奥列格 来瓶你从脖子上有洞的亲戚
Hey, Oleg, I need one of those $2 merlots
那里搞来的2块钱便宜红酒
you get from your cousin with the hole in his neck.
卡洛琳 价格检查
Caroline, price check.
08年柏菲酒庄干红 非常昂贵
Oh! Chateau pavie, 2008. Very expensive.
但我们值得拥有
But, hey, we deserve it.
让它呼吸一下新鲜空气[醒酒]
Here, better let it breathe.
它被我塞在我健身袋里
It was in my gym bag.
没问题
Not a problem.
这瓶好酒跟提臀内裤很搭
This vintage pairs well with jockstrap.
你说我还是白富美的时候 服务员也这么对我吗
Do you think waitresses did this to me when I had money?
看你当时摆不摆谱了
Only if you had an attitude.
那肯定是换过了
So that's a yes.
我都有点记不清 这画面
I can't remember if this reminds me
我是在大盗电影里看过
of an old heist movie I saw
还是我在当大盗时 亲自干过
or an old heist I actually participated in.
我们就像是7-11罗汉
I know. We're like Ocean's 7-11.
我们现在只缺一个柔软矮小
All we're missing is a tiny asian guy
能缩骨功进小盒子里的亚裔同党了
who can fit into small boxes.
你们在干嘛
Hello.
第十桌在催他们的酒了
Table ten is looking for their wine.
没问题 马上来
Oh, not a problem. Coming right up.
你们又干嘛了 为什么她面带微笑
What did you do? Why is she smiling?
我的裤子又着火了吗
Are my pants on fire again?
鼠辈 吃我一记
Oh, yeah, take that, sucker!
麦克斯 我说我们得让小蛋糕脱手
Max, when I said we need to move the cupcakes,
是指卖出去 不是脱手扔老鼠
I didn't mean through the air at a rodent's head.
它自己跑上窗子
Hey, he ran up the window,
现在正是我用"不退让法"的时刻啊
So it's kind of a stand-your-ground situation.
我跟它休战一会
Okay, we're on a time-out.
它在吃我的弹药
He's eating my ammo.
麦克斯生意又不行了
Max, business is down again,
我唯一说的比这句话次数更多的话
And the only phrase I've said more than that is,
是"神啊 在我睡梦中给个痛快吧"
"Please, God, take me in my sleep."
你看就知道 啥进展都没有
I mean, it's clear. Not getting ahead.
你是为了这个在闹脾气啊
Oh, is that what your mood is about?
因为你"没进展"
You're not getting any ahead?
我打通电话就能有人帮你"解决问题"哦
'Cause I can take care of that with one call.
你可别帮我跟你手机电话簿里
You are not hooking me up with that guy
名字是"口爆米花大师"的人牵线
who's listed in your phone as "Oral Redenbacher."
麦克斯 这是我们的未来
Max, this is our future.
我们得认真想怎么挣钱了
We need to get serious about making money.
必须的 我们今天早退吧
Absolutely. Let's leave early.
早退 你以为我们是啥 国会吗
Leave early? Who are we, congress?
你觉得别的生意会成功是靠早退吗
Do you think other business got successful by leaving early?
不是 他们是靠请便宜黑工
No, they did it by hiring illegals
以及把银行账户转移海外逃税
and moving their bank accounts offshore.
我们不能早退
We can't leave early.
招牌写着"开到半夜两点"
The sign says "Open till 2:00 A.M."
我也很"开"明 愿意写个"已关店"的新牌子
Well, I'm open to getting a new sign that says "Closed."
难道我们就得一直在这里
I mean, are we supposed to just hang around here
等着有什么疯子半夜光顾吗
and wait for whatever nut jobs are trolling around town?
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
你猜我和奥列格要去做哪件
Guess what Oleg and I are going to do
很可能会让我染丙肝的事情
that will probably give me Hep C.
跟汤米·李搞3P吗
A three way with Tommy Lee?
不是啦 傻瓜 我们要去刺情侣纹身
No, silly. We're getting matching tattoos.
我们想要刺能代表我们感情的图样
We want something that represents our relationship.
比如两只蝴蝶
So maybe two butterflies
在看《犯罪现场调查: 迈阿密》时大搞特搞
doing the nasty during "CSI: Miami."
哇 情侣纹身呢
Wow, you two, his and her tats.
生时好浪漫 死时好认尸
Romantic and will help identify the bodies.
是啊 情侣纹身算得上是
Sure, you know, matching tattoos
最深刻地表达承诺终身的方式
are the deepest expression of commitment.
情侣纹身
Well, matching tattoos
以及在对方面前拉屎吧
and pooping in front of each other.
我怎么会在我男人面前做这种事呢
I'm not gonna do it in front of my man.
我会去麦当劳拉 人家可是淑女哦
I poop at Mcdonald's 'cause I'm a lady.
谢谢你们的小蛋糕
Thanks for the cupcake.
我们真的得开始收她钱了
We really have to start charging her.
以什么名义"收"押她 一级收服男人罪吗
Charge her with what, first-degree man-settling?
麦克斯 正如我前面说的
Max, as I was saying,
我们得认真对待生意了
it's time to get serious about the business.
绝对的 咱们早退吧
Absolutely. Let's leave early.
干嘛 昨晚1点过后
What? Last night after 1:00,
我们只赚了15块钱 对吧
We made only $15, right?
干嘛 数学是我的强项
What? Math is my thing.
如果有天你站在阿姆面前时
Would you roll your eyes if you were standing
他开始唱饶舌 你也会翻白眼吗
across from Eminem and he started rapping?
会的
Uh, yes.
我会说"大爷你都要60了吧
I'd be all, "Dude, you're 60.
去前院的秋千上待着吧"
Sit on a porch swing."
来 这里是15块
Okay, look, here is $15.
这够付我们本来应该会赚到的钱了
That'll cover what we'll probably make.
我要闪人了
I'm leaving.
你要把我一个人丢下吗
You're just gonna leave me here?
没错 等你给我找完钱我就走
Yup, I'm leaving as soon as I get my change back
只要14块63不是吗
from that $14.63.
行啊 那你说我该找你多少呢
Fine, just tell me how much that is.
或是我立刻就走
Or maybe sooner.
这对我来说是个大日子
This is a very big day for me.
为什么 是因为我们突然接到
Why, because of this totally out-of-the-blue order
这商业座谈会的小蛋糕订单吗
we got to do cupcakes for this business seminar?
是我第一次从大门进这家连锁酒店
No, the first time I've entered a Sheridan through a door.
以前都是爬窗或是从货梯进
Usually it's by window or freight elevator.
有次我躲在一个女孩的成年礼服下 滚进来
And one time, I rolled in under some girl's Quinceanera dress.
座谈会马上开始了
The seminar's about to start.
没人认领的名牌还有潘蜜拉 艾伦
I have unclaimed name tags for Pamela, Ellen...
什么样的废物会来参加啊
What kind of losers would come to this?
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max, Caroline.
我不认为我们算废物啦
I wouldn't call us losers.
你们到了吗
Are you here?
好吧 其实小蛋糕订单是假的
Okay, so there is no cupcake order.
真相是我报名参加这个座谈会
I signed us up for this seminar.
我抱着小蛋糕挤地铁只是白做工吗
I carried cupcakes on a subway for nothing?
地铁上我隔壁的长舌妇一路都在烦我
The annoying woman next to me talked the whole time.
我就是坐在你隔壁的那个人 麦克斯
I was sitting next to you, Max.
我知道不这么做你根本不会来
Look, I knew you wouldn't come otherwise,
而你需要来参加
and you need to be here.
原来这是商业批斗会啊
This is a business intervention.
这不是批斗会好吗
It's not an intervention.
麦克斯 你最近的行为
Max, your behavior lately has affected me
由以下几种方式影响了我
in the following ways.
我信了你的邪
I can't believe this.
好歹我其他被批斗的时候 我还能醉着听
At least in my other interventions I was drunk.
我们需要这场座谈会
We need to do this seminar.
戈登·凯波是个天才
Gordon Kepper is a genius.
他能帮助我们生意向上冲一发
He's gonna give our business a real bump.
跟有毒品让我爽一发的男人厮混
Guys giving me a bump is why they threw me
就是我第二次被批斗时的主题
that second intervention.
走吧
Let's go.
不走 行啊 再见
Oh, mm, okay. See you.
所以这是你的新招吗 麦克斯
So this is your new thing, Max?
抛下我一个人自己走掉
You're just gonna walk out on me?
其实这是老招了
Actually, it's an old thing.
而且应该说是家族传统
In fact, it's kind of a family tradition.
我跟我爸学的 虽然不知道我爸是谁吧
I learned from my father, whoever he is.
别这样嘛 就两天而已
Come on. It's just two days.
还要两天 没门
Two days? No way.
下辈子吧
No freaking way.
里面有自助餐跟甜品吧
There's a buffet and a dessert bar.
那还不进去
Ooh, okay.
你稍等 我去付钱 我带了些钱
Wait here, I'll go pay. I brought some cash.
他们会收过期的百货现金礼劵对吧
And they'll take an expired Target gift card, right?
我们才不付钱
Oh, we are not paying.
给 给你 潘蜜拉
Here. Here, Pamela.
请跟着艾伦到货梯
Follow Ellen to the freight elevator.
不行 麦克斯 我们不能混进去
No way, Max. We are not sneaking in.
参加这个要多少钱
How much is this thing?
我们混进去吧 艾伦
We're sneaking in, Ellen.
今天 各位来到这里
Now, you all are here today
不只是为了认清你的生意
not only to find out what you are as a business
更是为了认清你们自己
but to find out who you are.
我是一个希望自助餐有起司通心粉的女人
I'm a lady hoping there's macaroni and cheese at that buffet.
而你 就是你的品牌
Who are you is your brand,
而说你的品牌只是个名字 就像在说
and saying that a brand is simply a name is like saying
亚伯拉罕·林肯只是个名字
Abraham Lincoln is simply a name,
圣雄甘地 上帝只是个名字
Or Mahatma Gandhi, God.
这家伙觉得自己是谁啊
Who does this guy think he is?
我知道你们一定在想"这家伙觉得自己是谁啊"
I'm sure you're wondering, "Who does this guy think he is?"
有点吓人啊
Okay, that was weird.
或许这有点吓人
Or maybe this seems weird.
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I've got chills.
每当谈到做生意 很多人都来问我
When it comes to business, people come up to me all the time.
他们说"戈登 做生意好难
They say, "Gordon, business is hard,
但我尽力而为了"
but I do what I can."
他们居然耸肩了 这态度对吗
And they shrug. Now, is that the right attitude?
-不对 -对啊
- No. - Yes.
对那些人 我告诉他们"别做你行的
To those people, I say, "Don't do what you can.
要行你做的"
Can what you do."
别做你行的
Don't do what you can.
要行你做的 懂吗 你们感受到了吗
Can what you do! Get it? Do you get it?
-懂了 -啥啊
- Yes. - No.
你才没懂呢
You did not get it.
大伙们看看自己椅子底下
All right, everybody, reach under your chairs
把你看到的东西捡起来
and pick up what you find there.
我希望能看到一条逃生之路
Hope it's a way out of here.
橡胶毛毛球
Koosh balls?
在那些桶子里 你们能发现
Inside those cans, you will find the key
打开生意成功之门的钥匙
to success in your business.
除非这钥匙是罗茜·奥唐纳
Not unless the key is Rosie O'Donnell's career
剪短发之前的事业
before her buzz cut.
实话
Truth.
这就是生意的大秘密
That's the big secret to business.
如果人们愿意对你说的话买账
If people buy what you're saying,
他们也会对你推销的东西买账
they will buy what you're selling.
麦克斯 提高警戒 一不小心这就变邪教了
Max, stay alert. This could go to cult like that.
我更愿意把你们手里握着的东西
I like to think of those things you're holding
想成是我的实话球[蛋蛋]
as my truth balls.
滚他丫的 咱们去吃肉丸吧
Screw this. Let's get to the meatballs.
接下来的两天中
Anytime in the next two days,
你们中的任何一人上台来推销
one of you is up here selling you something
你觉得狗屁不是的玩意
that you feel is just bull,
那就扔...
Then toss it--
麦克斯
Max!
我是叫 艾伦
I mean, Ellen!
是的 宝贝
Yeah, baby.
我说的就是这个意思
That is what I'm talking about.
扔球过来的那个人从心所愿 放胆去做
Whoever threw that is not afraid to really go for it,
能在商业道路上获得更长远的成功
and that will go a long way toward success in business.
行啊 但我想问离自助餐的道路还有多远
All right, cool, but it is a long way to the buffet?
老娘饿了
'Cause I am starving.
好的 各位
Okay, everyone.
你们要把自己被分配进的小组
Consider these small groups you've broken into
当做是个智囊团
as little think tanks.
我需要你们齐心协力 激荡出最好的自己
I need you to work together and bring out your very best.
麦克斯
Max!
别怪我睡着
Don't blame me.
怪刚才奶酪白酱意面里的鲜奶油吧
Blame the heavy cream at the fettuccini bar.
奶酪白酱是意大利话中"迷奸药"的意思吧
Alfredo must be italian for "roofie."
艾伦 说说你的生意
So, Ellen, tell us what you have,
我们会反馈给你评价
and I'll tell you what we think.
艾伦 是你啊
Oh, Ellen. That's you.
是的是的 是我
Oh, oh, yes, yes, that's me.
我是艾伦 一看就是叫艾伦的
I'm Ellen. Definitely an Ellen.
你看 我会跳舞哦
See, I dance.
好了
Okay.
好了好了 现在怪了
Okay. Okay, now it's weird.
所以 艾伦
So, Ellen...
来听听你的 超生品
Let's hear your B.B.B.--
超棒生意品牌
Your brilliant business brand.
我不是负责发言的 潘蜜拉才是负责发言的
I-I don't do the talking. Pamela does the talking.
潘
Pam?
谢谢 艾伦
Thanks, Ellen.
大家好 我叫潘...
Hello, everyone, my name is Pam...
姓潘宁
...Panning,
而我的搭档 艾伦 想要说的是
And what my partner, Ellen, was trying to say is,
我们是做非常有美感的手工达人小蛋糕
we making very beautiful artisan cupcakes.
还是很酷的哦
Yeah, but they're still cool.
我没说过它不酷啊
I never said they weren't cool.
可能是因为从你嘴里说出来
Yeah, mm, maybe they just didn't sound cool
所以听起来很不酷吧
coming out of your face.
那真是不好意思
I'm sorry, but at least actual words
但这也好过某人的"呃... 那个..."
are better than, "Uh, uh-uh, uh..."
女士们 请打住
Ladies, hold.
做生意 有时候
Sometimes in business
合伙船会开始往不同方向航行
partner ships will sail in two different directions,
所以你们要做的 就是想清楚
so you two need to find out if you're gonna continue
到底是渐行渐远 还是改变方向
to sail apart or if you're gonna change course
在名为"共识"的那个港口会合
and reconvene at the port of mutual understanding.
我们远也远不到哪去
Well, we can't sail too far apart
因为我还得跟她解释
'cause I'm definitely gonna have to explain
你刚才跟她说的话是啥意思
what you just said to her.
我懂啊
I got it.
我是一条船 我想要逃离你
I'm a boat, and I'm trying to get away from you.
完全说中我的心里话
Sounds right to me.
琢磨琢磨吧
Think it over.
再跟你的搭档[大副]好好聊聊
Talk it over with your first mate.
明天来上课时
Come back tomorrow
向我介绍你们的生意
and tell me who your business is,
而我会带领你们走向那里
and I'll help guide you toward that purpose.
要记得 "走向那里"中包含有
And remember, you can't purpose without--
-"那里"两字吗 -好了 别说了
- Puss. - Okay, wow.
戈登 她的船现在有点困在浅水区[肤浅]
Gordon, her boat's kind of in shallow water right now,
但我们会离开那里 解决问题
but we're gonna go away, get it together,
回来把你的旧看法吹走
and come back and blow you away.
"把你的旧看法吹走"里有"吹你..."
And you can't spell "Blow you away" without--
我们这艘船要走啦
Our ship's leaving.
你们好
Oh, hello.
欢迎来到威廉斯堡餐厅
Welcome to the Williamsburg diner.
两位想来点什么
Can I get you anything,
比如职业道德吗
like a work ethic?
阿憨 好会耍宝呀 但我们忙着呢
Han, this is adorable, but we're busy.
明天就要推销我们的商业品牌了
We're pitching our business brand tomorrow,
我和麦克斯必须意见一致
and Max and I need to get on the same page.
是啊 我们不想下半辈子都在这端盘子
Yeah, we don't want to work here the rest of our lives.
看来这点我们三人意见非常一致
Well, now we're all on the same page.
阿憨 就给我们十分钟嘛
Han, just give us ten minutes.
说完我们就去端盘子了
Then we'll get to work.
我都帮你们端了四年的盘子
Well, I've waited four years.
不在乎多端十分钟
What's another ten minutes?
麦克斯 不得不说我被
Max, I have to say I was a little thrown
你今天说的话惊到了
by that thing you said today.
什么 我这辈子最棒的性体验
What, that the best sex I've ever had
是独自坐游乐园的疯狂旋转椅吗
was alone on the Tilt-A-Whirl?
不 那为什么会惊到我 你每天都在说
No, why would that throw me? You say that every day.
不是 是你说我不酷那句话
No, that thing about me not sounding cool.
这为什么会惊到你 我每天都这么说
Why would that throw you? I say it every day.
是啊 但这次是针对我对商业的见解
Yes, but not about the business.
问题在哪儿 "手作达人"这个词吗
So what was it? The word "artisan"?
好吧 首先这个词听起来像"放屁大人"
Okay, first of all, it sounds like "fart-isan",
就像 "现在屋里有个放屁的大人"
as in, "A fart is in this room right now."
终于有人指认凶手出来了吧 卡洛琳
Somebody finally called you out on it, Caroline.
我想好了 我们的标语可以用
So I was thinking our slogan could be,
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕 又甜又香"
"Max's homemade cupcakes. Sugar and spice."
我宁愿选择"放屁达人"
I'd rather go with fart-isan.
真的吗 瘪四
Really, Beavis?
你的生意伙伴大头蛋有什么好建议吗
What does your business partner butthead think?
我们现在生意惨淡
Our business isn't working.
猜猜谁更惨
Well, guess who is working.
我 倒霉的老板
Me, the damn owner.
你干嘛觉得意外
Why are you surprised?
你最清楚有多少小蛋糕卖不出去
You know how many cupcakes were not selling.
我是说 你每晚至少偷吃六个
I mean, you're secretly eating at least six a night
好让我觉得我们是多卖了六个
to make me think we're selling more.
也是因为我难过好吗
Also 'cause I'm sad.
我知道你从沃顿毕业懂得多 但是...
Look, I know you went to Wharton and all, but--
等等
Wait...
现在是什么情况
What's happening?
专门针对我的商业批斗会吗
Is this a business intervention on me?
你个主办人连"商业"都能念成
From someone who pronounces the word business
"丧业"
"Bidness"?
你干嘛瞪大眼睛一脸惊讶啊
Why are you giving me the big eye-painting face?
你自己也知道现在生意惨淡啊
You knew the business wasn't working.
那我从未听过你提任何改善的办法啊
Well, I don't hear you coming up with any ideas.
那是因为你根本不听
That's 'cause you don't listen.
还记得我以前说过我们应该
Remember when I said we should stop making
比如写着"吃屎"和"滚蛋"那种
like "Eat it" and "Lick me"?
你宏大的商业计划就是
Your big business plan is cupcakes
写着"吃屎"和"滚蛋"的小蛋糕吗
that say "Eat it" and "Lick me"?
还有其他哏王蛋糕 比如"废柴"
And other funny things like "Loser"
或"有苦自己吞"
or "Eat your feelings."
那何不直接在人们来窗口买蛋糕时
Hmm, why not just shoot people in the face
一枪打爆他们的头呢
when they come to the window?
我想过在我们的T恤后面印上
And I thought the back of our T-shirt could just say,
"奶油[精液]满满"
"Cream filled."
如果是一个辣妹穿 一定超有哏呀
So funny if, like, a hot girl was wearing it.
如果是一个胖子穿 那就更搞笑了
And even funnier if it was a fat guy.
好吧 或许被戈登说中了
Okay, maybe like Gordon said,
我们的合伙船在往不同方向航行
our partner ships are going in different directions.
我的香甜可口号开往这边
My sugar and spice ship is going one way,
你的毒丑酗酒号开往另一边
and your mean and ugly booze cruise is going another.
所以不如明天我开我的船
So how about tomorrow, I'll sail my ship,
你开你的船 艾伦
and you can sail yours, Ellen.
好啊
Done.
潘 我知道你觉得你那艘船不会沉
And, Pam, I know you think your ship don't sink,
但你错了
but it does.
汉娜 托德 开始吧
So, Hannah, Todd, go.
告诉大家 你们的生意是什么
Tell us, who is your business?
对 就是外表像吉他箱形状的行李箱
Yeah, they're suitcases that look like guitar cases
你在机场拎着时 一看就酷炫
so you can look cool at the airport.
目前为止 没人扔实话球
So far, no truth balls.
那意味着我们相信你们对自己的阐述
That means we believe you're telling some truth
是实话
of who you are.
商业向来...
Business is always--
那好吧
Okay then.
怎么了 他们的创意
So what, their big idea
就是把行李塞进吉他箱里吗
is just throwing your crap in a guitar case?
谁敢跟你的放屁大人小蛋糕比啊
Well, it's no fart-isan cupcake.
托德 汉娜 你们有跟我们的绘图画家碰面
Todd, Hannah, did you get together with our graphic artist
设计出一个商标吗
to help create a logo?
有啊
Yes, we did.
我们忙活了一晚 老实说
We stayed up all night, and to be honest,
出来的效果有点奇怪
it got kind of weird.
那就是我们的商标
That's our logo,
我们公司的名字叫
And our company's called
"我是乐队的人"
"I'm with the band."
住手
Back off!
她刚从戒毒所出来好吗
She just got out of rehab.
商业不适合胆小的人
Business is not for the faint of heart
也不适合瘾君子
or coke addicts.
下一对 我们有请艾伦和潘
Next up, we've got Ellen and Pam.
让我们以爱的掌声欢迎她们
Let's give 'em some love.
麦克斯 你不会真的上台
Max, you're really not gonna go up there
把你的馊主意当商业计划卖吧
and sell your idea as a business plan.
真的啊 而且我挺有信心的
Yup, and I feel pretty good about it.
好吧 那我希望你会享受满脸球[蛋蛋]的滋味
Okay, well, then I hope you enjoy lots of balls in your face.
我去火人节时都没碰过了
If I didn't at Burning Man,
我才不信这里会有机会
I doubt I will here.
戈登 你好
Gordon, hi.
正如你所预言的
As you predicted,
今天我们会分开展示各自的品牌
today we'll be presenting our brands separately.
好的 看样子我们要看到品牌大战了
Okay, looks like we have us a brand off, folks.
这太令人激动了
This is exciting.
我也感受到了
I am feeling it!
艾伦 我知道你不习惯独自一人
Ellen, I know you're not used to being alone.
我也是 所以我娶了第三任妻子
Neither was I, hence wife number three.
别着急
Don't rush.
花点时间静下心 集中注意力
Take some time to get yourself centered.
哟哟哟 在场的各位好
Yo, yo, yo! What's happening, Sheridan!
艾伦在这里
Ellen in the house.
来点欢呼吧
Let me hear some noise.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
有人不爽了 不过没关系
We got some haters. That's cool.
艾伦 你有设计商标吗
Ellen, did you design a logo?
当然有 给他们看看 狼友
Sure did. Show it, player.
乔治 她在说你呢
George, she's talking to you.
视觉冲击力不错
Oh, good impact..
好 小蛋糕生意
Boom, cupcake business.
但是...
But, um...
你的生意名在哪里呢
where's the name of your business.
我不想要
Oh, I didn't want one.
我只要显得酷就行
I just wanted it to be cool.
那正确的意思是
So let me get this correct.
你想为自己的生意做T恤
You want to make t-shirts for your business
但又跟你的生意无关
with no business connection.
好吧
Okay.
这是你选择的路 但很可能只能走到这步了
This is your journey, but it might end here.
不不不 看 这是一个小蛋糕
No, no, no, see, it's a cupcake,
而我们卖的就是小蛋糕 所以多"丧业"啊
and we sell cupcakes, so that's the "Bidness."
算了 滚你们的
Okay, you know what? Screw this!
这T恤超级酷 如果你们感受不到
That t-shirt is way cool, and if you can't see it,
那说明这座谈会超不值我付的一千块
this seminar is so not worth the $1,000 I paid.
再见
Peace out.
在商界 我们称这为"彻底垮台"[崩溃]
In business, we call that a meltdown.
屡见不鲜
It happens.
现在让我们有请艾伦的前搭档 潘
So why don't we bring up Ellen's former partner Pam.
让我们以热烈的掌声欢迎潘
Let's give Pam a round of applause.
麦克斯 我不一定非要上台
Max, I don't have to go up there.
走吧 我们回去吧
Come on, we can just leave.
现在是谁想背起吉他行李箱灰溜溜逃跑
Oh, look who wants to pack up their guitar suitcase and go.
我说走是因为你太烂 给你留面子好吗
You know what? I was only leaving 'cause you failed.
我对我的点子信心十足
I believe in my ideas.
下午好 各位好
Good afternoon. Hello, hi.
我代表麦克斯自制小蛋糕
I represent Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
我要先打断你
I'm gonna stop you right there.
为什么是麦克斯的小蛋糕
Why Max's cupcakes?
为什么不是艾伦或潘的
Why not Ellen's or Pam's?
这个嘛...
Well, um...
麦克斯是一位非常特别的人
Max was--Max is this very special person
是她启发了我们整个事业
and the inspiration behind our whole business.
懂了
Got it.
所以麦克斯是你和你事业的情感试金石
So Max is an emotional touchstone
是的
Yes.
有理有据 请继续
Valid. Go on.
很好
Great.
请看商标...
So the logo--
乔治
George.
这是我们现在的公司形象
This is our current company logo,
我觉得效果还行
And I feel it works just fine.
有句话说得好 "如果没坏 干嘛要修"
I mean, if it ain't broke, don't fix it, right?
好吧
OKAY.
小蛋糕的图案象征甜美
Well, the cupcake shows a mix of sweet imagery
而我们是两个试图走复古风重新定义
because we're two girls trying to retro-repurpose the phrase
"又香又甜 花好月圆"这句话的女孩
"Sugar and spice and everything nice."
住手 住手 住手 住手
Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
别扔了
Leave Pam alone!
我没事 艾伦
I'm fine, Ellen.
他们阻挡不了我 因为我对我们有信心
They can't shut me down, because I believe in us
对我们的手作达人小蛋糕有信心
and our special brand of artisan cupcakes.
你找扔呢
Why?
话筒给我
Give me!
吃屎吧 废柴们 吃屎吃屎
Eat it, you losers! Eat it, eat it!
我看见实话球停下了
I see the truth balls have stopped.
看来"吃屎吧 废柴们"
It looks like "Eat it, eat it, you losers,"
可以当你们的品牌名啊
might just be your brand.
你们俩就是一个甜 一个香
You two are a combination of sugar and spice
以及花不好 月不圆
and things not so nice.
说到实话 你们得向桑德拉支付本次座谈会的费用
Speaking of truth, I need you to pay Sandra for the seminar.
虽然我很敬佩你们的勇气
As much as I admire your pluck,
但你连吃12回的意大利面可不免费
12 trips to the pasta bar aren't free.
走吧 潘
Come on, Pam.
我们走 艾伦
Yeah, let's go, Ellen.
我是艾伦
I'm Ellen.
猜猜我外套下面藏着什么
Guess what I have under my coat.
我知道肯定不是缩过的胸
Well, I know it's not a boob reduction.
你觉得怎么样 很酷吧
What do you think? Cool, huh?
天啊 外面已经有卖这设计了吗
Aw, man, somebody already makes that?
真扫兴
Oh, bummer.
就好像当时我以为自己发明了炸薯条三明治
This is like when I thought I invented chip-wiches.
早该猜到了 我当时正吃着呢
Should've known. I was eating one at the time.
不 麦克斯 这是你设计的T恤
No, Max, this is your shirt.
我从座谈会拿来设计稿
I got the rendering from the seminar
然后定做的
and had it made at
就在"一小时内包搞定"公司做的
We Can Make Anything In Under An Hour.
地址就在桥底
You know, that place under the bridge
挨着你被逮捕的那家未成年人酒吧
near the underage bar where you got under arrest.
不是吧
No way.
不是吧 太性感了
Oh, no way. That's hot.
我知道 那家店的女职员
I know, and a girl at the place
还问我这衣服在哪里买的呢
asked me where she could get one.
真的吗
Really?
现在我都有点爱上自己了
Kind of in love with myself right now.
是什么让你改变主意的
Hey, what made you change your mind about the t-shirts?
我在沃顿学到的其中一件事就是
Well, one of the things I learned at Wharton
成功在于能敞开怀拥抱一个更好的主意
is that success depends on staying open to a better idea,
即使那不是自己的
even if it's not yours.
给
And here.
我觉得你更喜欢黑的
I thought you'd rather a black one.
约炮爱黑人 生活爱黑衣
On Tinder and in life.